fancystreems.com 2017-11-28

# Privacy Policy - FancyStreems.Com

**FancyStreems Privacy Policy**

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of FancyStreems. If you do not agree to the Policy, please do not use this site. FancyStreems reviews its privacy policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. This page should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. If you want to communicate with us about our policy, please e-mail us at: admin@FancyStreems.Com, which operates the Internet site located at www.fancystreems.com, recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to our sites. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to our sites. Personally identifiable information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted.

**Third Party Stream/Links**

FancyStreems has established many links directly to sites operated by third parties. These sites are not operated or maintained by FancyStreems. These sites may collect personal information from you. You should check the applicable privacy policy's of the third party site's in case you enter these sites. All links to external sites (not FancyStreems's) are opened in a new window! 

FancyStreems chooses its advertisers and business partners carefully. However, FancyStreems is not responsible for the content or practices of Web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. These links are meant for the user's convenience only. Links to third party sites do not constitute sponsorship, endorsement or approval by FancyStreems of the content, policies or practices of such third party sites. Once you enter a third party site by such a link, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site.

**Copy Right Claims and DMCA**

Please note that the channels/streams used by us are all from third party websites, freely available from third party streaming server sources, we do not own or claim to own those third party streams/links. We respect the copy right laws and we never intend to harm the copy rights of the respective owners of the streams/events. FancyStreems.Com does not control the streams/videos and we do not take any responsibility about these third party website/streams/links about the quality of content, performance and privacies. Additionally, FancyStreems.Com can not filter or censor the content of any third-party website streams/links. By surfing the web site, you expressly relieve FancyStreems.Com from all liabilities arising from your use of any such streams which are obviously belongs to third party. Consequently, we have a tendency to encourage you to bear in mind after you leave the FancyStreems.Com and to study the terms and conditions and privacy policy of every site that you simply visit. FancyStreems.Com in general searches the relevant Tv Streams from different Sources and re-produced them. The video streams originated by external websites, which is not connected with FancyStreems.Com, as a result of its associate aggregation of many channels, the TV Brands have several copyright house owners. FancyStreems.Com has established several links on to sites operated by third parties Who transmit the video streams. These sites don't operate or maintained by FancyStreems.Com.

**Notice**

FancyStreems will notify you when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you and how we intend to use it. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with information you requested, in connection with entry forms, or in connection with community postings such as chat and bulletin boards. Sometimes FancyStreems engages in activities with business partners and sponsors with whom personal information is jointly collected or shared. We will try to make it clear at the time of collection who is asking for and/or sharing your information. In situations where your information will be shared, it is recommended that you also review the privacy policy of our business partner or sponsor.

**Use and Security**

Personally identifiable information that visitors submit to our sites is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted unless we disclose other uses in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. Such other uses may include sending you information or materials we think you will find interesting, or sharing the information with FancyStreems's Media's advertisers and reputable business partners. However, at the time of collection, you will have the option of instructing us not to send you additional information or share your personal information with third parties. FancyStreems is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of our business partners. FancyStreems may use reputable third parties to manage activities available on our sites including, but not limited to statistical analysis, or chats. These parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities. Similarly, we may contract with third parties to handle the fulfillment of subscriptions or requests for information you submit to our sites, such as sending you a newsletter. In most instances, FancyStreems instructs these third parties to use personally identifiable information only for the specific purpose for which it is collected, and not to sell, market or transfer such information to other entities. If FancyStreems obtains personal information that has been collected from you by a third party, including our business partners, this Privacy Policy nonetheless governs FancyStreems's use of that information. Please remember that any information posted on bulletin boards and/or communicated in chat areas becomes public information. You should use caution when sharing information as any of it can be collected and used by people you may not know. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to divulge any personal information. While FancyStreems strives to protect and respect your privacy, we can not guarantee the security of any information you disclose in a chat room or bulletin board and you do so at your own risk. FancyStreems may use personally identifiable information in aggregate form to make our sites better and more responsive to the needs of our visitors. This statistical compilation and analysis of information may also be used by FancyStreems or provided to others, in aggregate, for marketing, advertising or research purposes. If at any time after submitting your personal information to our sites you would no longer like to receive information from us, simply follow the "unsubscribe" directions at the end of any email communication you receive. FancyStreems does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. Personal information may be disclosed in special situations where FancyStreems has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering (intentionally or unintentionally) with FancyStreems's rights, property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. Also, FancyStreems may reveal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. FancyStreems maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our sites, and periodically reviews and updates its security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Although FancyStreems strives to protect your personal information, we can not ensure or warranty the security of any information you may transmit to us. This is done so at your own risk. Once we do receive your transmission, however, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.

**Cookies**

Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most Web sites, including those operated by FancyStreems, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. Our Cookies are no programs that can cause damage to a user's systems or files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. But you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with features such as adding your personal favourites.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on FancyStreems.Com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**January 01, 2013**

� 2013-2020, FancyStreems, The World of Quality Streaming!
